[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "Gloria Allred, should we assume from this fairly dramatic action by the state attorney that they have got evidence that we are not aware of?", "question_tokens": ["Gloria", "Allred", ",", "should", "we", "assume", "from", "this", "fairly", "dramatic", "action", "by", "the", "state", "attorney", "that", "they", "have", "got", "evidence", "that", "we", "are", "not", "aware", "of", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "Well, they definitely have evidence that we are not aware of and they're not revealing that evidence, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "definitely", "have", "evidence", "that", "we", "are", "not", "aware", "of", "and", "they", "'re", "not", "revealing", "that", "evidence", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gloria Allred"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "Gloria, if you were prosecuting this case, where would you think the weaknesses are in George Zimmerman's case from everything you've seen and heard?", "question_tokens": ["Gloria", ",", "if", "you", "were", "prosecuting", "this", "case", ",", "where", "would", "you", "think", "the", "weaknesses", "are", "in", "George", "Zimmerman", "'s", "case", "from", "everything", "you", "'ve", "seen", "and", "heard", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "Well, I would be thinking about where the flaws are, and I would be interested in also what he allegedly has told family members who have appeared on television, whether there are inconsistencies in what he has told the police, depending on what he has told the police.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "be", "thinking", "about", "where", "the", "flaws", "are", ",", "and", "I", "would", "be", "interested", "in", "also", "what", "he", "allegedly", "has", "told", "family", "members", "who", "have", "appeared", "on", "television", ",", "whether", "there", "are", "inconsistencies", "in", "what", "he", "has", "told", "the", "police", ",", "depending", "on", "what", "he", "has", "told", "the", "police", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "Eric, how would you describe the mood down there, following this announcement today?", "question_tokens": ["Eric", ",", "how", "would", "you", "describe", "the", "mood", "down", "there", ",", "following", "this", "announcement", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "EX", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "I would say among officials down here it's probably a little bit of relief.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "say", "among", "officials", "down", "here", "it", "'s", "probably", "a", "little", "bit", "of", "relief", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "How important has their demeanor, their behavior been?", "question_tokens": ["How", "important", "has", "their", "demeanor", ",", "their", "behavior", "been", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "Oh, I think that's very important.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "think", "that", "'s", "very", "important", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 149, "question": "What is your reaction and the family's reaction to the arrest and the charging of your brother, George?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reaction", "and", "the", "family", "'s", "reaction", "to", "the", "arrest", "and", "the", "charging", "of", "your", "brother", ",", "George", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "Piers, obviously as a family, we're devastated.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "obviously", "as", "a", "family", ",", "we", "'re", "devastated", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "How do you feel about the fact it's been such a tough charge?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "the", "fact", "it", "'s", "been", "such", "a", "tough", "charge", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "Well, I agree.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "agree", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "When did you last see him?", "question_tokens": ["When", "did", "you", "last", "see", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "IMMERMAN: Right.", "answer_tokens": ["IMMERMAN", ":", "Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "JJ", "CC", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP$", "JJ", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "Are you concerned about that?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "concerned", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "We are -- our concerns go in the order, first and foremost, obviously, of safety for his life, then his well-being, then it's our life and our well-being.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "are", "--", "our", "concerns", "go", "in", "the", "order", ",", "first", "and", "foremost", ",", "obviously", ",", "of", "safety", "for", "his", "life", ",", "then", "his", "well-being", ",", "then", "it", "'s", "our", "life", "and", "our", "well-being", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "Which way is he running?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "way", "is", "he", "running", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "Down towards the other entrance to the neighborhood.", "answer_tokens": ["Down", "towards", "the", "other", "entrance", "to", "the", "neighborhood", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "Which entrance is that that he's heading towards?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "entrance", "is", "that", "that", "he", "'s", "heading", "towards", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "The back entrance.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "back", "entrance", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "Are you following him?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "following", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "You know, why did your brother take out a gun and shoot an unarmed teenager?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "why", "did", "your", "brother", "take", "out", "a", "gun", "and", "shoot", "an", "unarmed", "teenager", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "Do you understand that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "understand", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "I do understand that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "understand", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VB", "NN", "IN", "``", "NNS", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 298, "question": "It's his blood that's lying there, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "his", "blood", "that", "'s", "lying", "there", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "POS", "VBG", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "Well, I do take exception with \"follows.\"", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "take", "exception", "with", "``", "follows", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "IN", "NNPS", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "Let me ask you, Robert, why was George carrying a gun to target?", "question_tokens": ["Let", "me", "ask", "you", ",", "Robert", ",", "why", "was", "George", "carrying", "a", "gun", "to", "target", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "Thousands of Floridians have enacted laws to make sure that they are able to carry guns.", "answer_tokens": ["Thousands", "of", "Floridians", "have", "enacted", "laws", "to", "make", "sure", "that", "they", "are", "able", "to", "carry", "guns", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Robert", "George"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "RP", ":", "NN", "IN", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 327, "question": "What was he doing after that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "he", "doing", "after", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "Again, that's an element of the case that will come out -- come out in --", "answer_tokens": ["Again", ",", "that", "'s", "an", "element", "of", "the", "case", "that", "will", "come", "out", "--", "come", "out", "in", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"]}, "docId": "120411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "What did he tell you that explains why he continued walking towards Trayvon Martin?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "he", "tell", "you", "that", "explains", "why", "he", "continued", "walking", "towards", "Trayvon", "Martin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNS", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "Well, he didn't continue -- he didn't continue to walk towards Trayvon Martin.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "did", "n't", "continue", "--", "he", "did", "n't", "continue", "to", "walk", "towards", "Trayvon", "Martin", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "But how do you explain that your brother is one bang away during this terrible beating from wearing diapers and being fed by you for the rest of his life, and the fact that within a matter of just a couple of hours, we see him walking around the police station perfectly OK?", "question_tokens": ["But", "how", "do", "you", "explain", "that", "your", "brother", "is", "one", "bang", "away", "during", "this", "terrible", "beating", "from", "wearing", "diapers", "and", "being", "fed", "by", "you", "for", "the", "rest", "of", "his", "life", ",", "and", "the", "fact", "that", "within", "a", "matter", "of", "just", "a", "couple", "of", "hours", ",", "we", "see", "him", "walking", "around", "the", "police", "station", "perfectly", "OK", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "CC", "RB", ",", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "How do you react to that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "react", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "Well, you know, first and foremost, the most important reaction is to understand that independent analysis like that is not admissible.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "first", "and", "foremost", ",", "the", "most", "important", "reaction", "is", "to", "understand", "that", "independent", "analysis", "like", "that", "is", "not", "admissible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 416, "question": "Which hospital did he have the broken nose reset?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "hospital", "did", "he", "have", "the", "broken", "nose", "reset", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "Piers, I'm not getting into specifics about what doctor treated him, how he was treated.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "getting", "into", "specifics", "about", "what", "doctor", "treated", "him", ",", "how", "he", "was", "treated", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}, "docId": "120411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "Why didn't he leave it to the police?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "n't", "he", "leave", "it", "to", "the", "police", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "George did leave it to the police.", "answer_tokens": ["George", "did", "leave", "it", "to", "the", "police", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "But he didn't, though, did he?", "question_tokens": ["But", "he", "did", "n't", ",", "though", ",", "did", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "IN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "No, he did.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "he", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "What would you say to them tonight?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "say", "to", "them", "tonight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "You know, as the family for us, we have nothing left to give.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "as", "the", "family", "for", "us", ",", "we", "have", "nothing", "left", "to", "give", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["George"]}, "docId": "120411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "RBS", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "What did you make of it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "Well, obviously, the most information is going to come from George himself.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "obviously", ",", "the", "most", "information", "is", "going", "to", "come", "from", "George", "himself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"]}, "docId": "120411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 581, "question": "Given the amount of stress he's under, given the fact that he's been on the run, effectively, for the last month or so, would it be a surprise that he's suffering from a psychiatric damage by now?", "question_tokens": ["Given", "the", "amount", "of", "stress", "he", "'s", "under", ",", "given", "the", "fact", "that", "he", "'s", "been", "on", "the", "run", ",", "effectively", ",", "for", "the", "last", "month", "or", "so", ",", "would", "it", "be", "a", "surprise", "that", "he", "'s", "suffering", "from", "a", "psychiatric", "damage", "by", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "AYLOR: You know, it's hard to say that without talking to him, because Trayvon Martin's parents have been under a lot of stress too.", "answer_tokens": ["AYLOR", ":", "You", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "hard", "to", "say", "that", "without", "talking", "to", "him", ",", "because", "Trayvon", "Martin", "'s", "parents", "have", "been", "under", "a", "lot", "of", "stress", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]